Hope. Healing. Health.
======================

Privacy Policy
==============

### NeuroStim TMS Centers LLC

_Last Updated On March 5th, 2023_

NeuroStimTMS.com is serious about protecting your online privacy. This Privacy Statement explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as a user of our website.

NeuroStim TMS Centers, LLC and NeuroStim TMS, PS (“us”, “we”, “our”, “NeuroStim) together operate the www.neurostimtms.com website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from www.neurostimtms.com.

### Definitions:

* Service: Service is the www.neurostimtms.com website operated by NeuroStim
* Personal Data: Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).
* Usage Data: Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
* Cookies: Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
* Data Controller: Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.
* Data Processors (or Service Providers): Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the
* Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.
* Data Subject (or User): Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

### Information We Collect And Use:

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* First name and last name
* Email address
* Phone number
* State, City
* ​Data about how you use our website
* ​Technical data such as details about your browser, time zone settings and other technology on the devise you use to access our website
* Your marketing and communication preferences
* Any information that you directly provide to us whether through our contact form, over the phone, by email or otherwise
* Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information. Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* Session Cookies – We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
* Preference Cookies – We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
* Security Cookies – We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

### Use of Data:

NeuroStim uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service
* To notify you about changes to our Service
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
* ​To provide customer support
* ​To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
* ​To monitor the usage of our Service
* ​To detect, prevent and address technical issues
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already received or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):

NeuroStim’s legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

NeuroStim may process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights
* ​For payment processing purposes
* To comply with the law

### Retention of Data:

NeuroStim will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. NeuroStim will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Transfer of Data:

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. NeuroStim will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Disclosure of Data:

#### Business Transaction

If NeuroStim is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

#### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, NeuroStim may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

#### Legal Requirements

NeuroStim may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend the rights or property of NeuroStim
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* ​To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* To protect against legal liability

### Security of Data:

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### “Do Not Track” Signals:

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):

You have certain data protection rights under the GDPR regulation. NeuroStim aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us at hr@neurostimtms.com.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you: Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data. Please contact us at hr@neurostimtms.com to assist you.
* The right of rectification: You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
* The right to object: You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
* ​The right of restriction: You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
* ​The right to data portability: You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
* ​The right to withdraw consent: You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where NeuroStim relied on your consent to process your personal information.

To register a complaint regarding GDPR, or simply want more information, please contact our EU representative at: [Lez@neurostimtms.com](mailto:Lez@neurostimtms.com). Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

### Your California Privacy Rights:

This notice to California residents is provided under California law, including the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”). This notice supplements our Privacy Policy by explaining your California privacy rights if you are a California resident, and provides certain mandated disclosures about our treatment of California residents’ information, both online and offline.

#### Right to Access

If you are a California resident, you have the right to request, up to two times each year, access to categories and specific pieces of personal information about you that we collect, use, disclose, and sell.

#### Right to Delete

If you are a California resident, you have the right to request that we delete personal information that we collect from you, subject to applicable legal exceptions.

#### Process to Make a CCPA Request

To make an access or deletion request, please contact us at hr@neurostimtms.com. Before completing your request, we may need to verify your identity or the identity of your authorized representative. We will send you a link to verify your email address and may request additional documentation or information solely for the purpose of verifying your identity. You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of your privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.

#### Removal of Content

If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any site where this policy is posted, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted.

To make such a request, please send an email with a detailed description of the specific content or information to hr@neurostimtms.com. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.

### Service Providers:

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics:

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

* Google Analytics – Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en

### Behavioral Remarketing:

NeuroStim uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

* **Google Ads** – Google Ads/AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [https://www.google.com/settings/adsGoogle](https://adssettings.google.com/anonymous?hl=en) also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)
* **Facebook Ads** – Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc. You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: [https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950) To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217) Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA [https://www.aboutads.info/choices/](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/) the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada [https://youradchoices.ca/](https://youradchoices.ca/) or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe [https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) or opt-out using your mobile device settings. For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)
* ​**Twitter Ads** – Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc. You can opt-out from Twitter’s interest-based ads by following their instructions: [https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405) You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: [https://twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/privacy)
* **​LinkedIn Ads** – LinkedIn remarketing service is provided by LinkedIn Ireland Unlimited Company. You can opt-out from LinkedIn’s interest-based ads by following their instructions: [https://www.linkedin.com/psettings/advertising/actions-that-showed-interest](https://www.linkedin.com/psettings/advertising/actions-that-showed-interest) You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of LinkedIn by visiting their Privacy Policy page: [https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)

**If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads;** you may opt-out of the tracking and remarketing services mentioned above by visiting: [https://optout.networkadvertising.org/](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/) or [https://optout.aboutads.info/](https://optout.aboutads.info/) (or if located in the European Union, by clicking here: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](https://youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising, you will continue to receive generic ads.

### Mobile Phone Number:

No mobile numbers will be shared with third parties/affiliates for marketing/promotional purposes. All the categories herein exclude text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties.

a) Reply Stop to opt-out, Reply Help for Help.  
b) Message Frequency May Vary.  
c) Data Rates May Apply  
d) Carriers are not liable for undelivered messages.

### Links to Other Sites:

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children’s Privacy:

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us at hr@neurostimtms.com. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy:

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [Lez@neurostimtms.com](mailto:lez@neurostimtms.com) or by mail using the details below.

Re: Privacy Compliance Officer

NeuroStim TMS Centers  
10700 Meridian AVE N, Suite 406,  
Seattle, WA 98133,  
United States of America

Download Our Free **NeuroStim TMS Therapy** Brochure
----------------------------------------------------

[Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation Therapy](https://neurostimtms.com/) > **Privacy Policy**

#### NeuroStim

#### Our AZ Clinics

#### Our WA Clinics

#### Contact Us









© Copyright 2017-2024 | NeuroStim TMS
